Henry Claude Bernardin

347.236.5657 Cell Henry.Bernardin@gmail.com Email www.HenryBernardin.com Website

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a committed professional with over five years of managerial and administrative experience, and a year of front-end software development experience, seeking to assume a software development/ UI design role, which will facilitate continued personal and professional growth. I enjoy working with others to achieve an objective on time and with excellence.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Front-End Software Developer & Designer

New York, NY—2019-Present

- Communicate with clients to deliver quality software projects and follow up to ensure that the customer is satisfied with product
- Develop custom front-end HTML, CSS, & JavaScript websites
- Configure domain names and hosting through Netlify.com

Program Manager, Cerebral Palsy Associations of New York State New York, NY—2016-Present

- Responsible for ensuring compliance with all state and federally mandated requirements pertaining to the program (OMRDD, OSHA, COA, Medicaid, etc.)
- Documentation, review and submission of all financial accounts, ledgers associated with personal allowance, earned income and members in house ledgers for cash on hand, including staff payroll, and site expenditures
- Ensure the proper reporting, investigation and review of all incidents relative to OPWDD Part 624 regulations and the Justice Center

Assistant Program Manager, Catholic Charities Neighborhood Services

Brooklyn, NY -2014-2016

- Supervised and ensured completion of apartment inspections and fire drills
- Provided support in order to ensure constant audit readiness and regulatory compliance of all records, services, and maintenance issues
- Responsible for assisting in training of all policies, procedures in accordance with OPwDD regulations and guidelines

EDUCATION

City University of New York- Brooklyn College

B.S., Double Major in Health Nutrition Sciences & Psychology — 2006-2010

SKILLS SUMMARY

Languages/Computer/Administrative

Haitian Creole (fluent), Spanish (intermediate), HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Sass, Responsive Design, Testing/Debugging, UI Design, Git/GitHub, Bootstrap, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint, Adobe Photoshop (intermediate), Microsoft Word, Outlook (advanced)

CERTIFICATIONS

FreeCodeCamp.org

Responsive Web Design – 12/2018

Chingu.io

Chingu Voyage 12 - 11/2019